export const data = [
    {
        
        question:" The acronyms ITES stands for _?",
        option1:"Information Technology Entrusted Systems",
        option2:"Information Technology Extended Services",
        option3:"Information Technology Enabled Services",
        option4:"Information Technology Enlighted Services",
        ans:3,
    },
    {
        question:" Which of these is not a feature of java?",
        option1:"Object-oriented",
        option2:"Platform-independent",
        option3:"Compiled",
        option4:"Interpreted language",
        ans:3,

    },
    {
        question:"What is the language is used write Flutterapps?",
        option1:"Java",
        option2:"Kotlin",
        option3:"Swift",
        option4:"Dart",
        ans:4,

    },{
        question:"What is the difference between 'float' and 'double' in C?",
        option1:"Syntax only",
        option2:"Precision",
        option3:"Usage",
        option4:"No difference",
        ans:2,

    },{
        question:"Which keyword is used to remove table from database?",
        option1:"DROP",
        option2:"DELETE",
        option3:"REMOVE",
        option4:"ALTER",
        ans:1,

    },{
        question:"Which property is used to change textcolor of element?",
        option1:"text-color",
        option2:"color",
        option3:"font-color",
        option4:"background-color",
        ans:2,

    },{
        question:"In operating systems, a semaphore is a _:",
        option1:"A type of malware",
        option2:"A low-level programming language",
        option3:"A signal mechanism",
        option4:"An I/O device driver",
        ans:3,

    },{
        question:"Which of these is not a Python built-in datatype?",
        option1:"dict",
        option2:"array",
        option3:"set",
        option4:"frozenset",
        ans:2,

    },{
        question:"Which topology does the Internet resemble?",
        option1:"Mesh",
        option2:"Ring",
        option3:"Star",
        option4:"Bus",
        ans:1,

    },{
        question:"JSX stands for...",
        option1:"JavaScript XML",
        option2:"Java Syntax Extension",
        option3:"JavaScript Syntax",
        option4:"Java Structured XML",
        ans:1,

    },];